I had a probe that says, Kate says, the Kate show.
Since someone wants to spread the narrative
that I donated thousands to a groomer,
I figured I'd address it.
This is absolutely not true.
It's less than $200.
You're running with lies.
The gratification I got from watching him crawl out
of his skin while doing it and doing it well played
was worth it.
Doing it and doing it well.
I remember that.
Doing it and doing it doing it well.
You played that?
I didn't hear that.
I crawled out of my skin though.
Okay.
Interesting.
No, you fucking retard. He doesn't understand. He doesn't get it. He doesn't get it
He doesn't get it
Y'all he doesn't get it
That community post was for talking about Zae and not him. I
Donated less than two hundred dollars and it was all for doing it and doing it well songs to Gaia not you retard
All right, really. We're just here to restream. I'll try to keep my commentary to a minimum
But yeah, I'm just here to provide a
An alternative place to watch Psycho Psyche
I mean I watched the video as I was Shrek I
Was like I don't really watch kids movies. So I turned it off
Because I'm not that big of a fan of Shrek, but
Straight does it mean big band or something like that? I'm not sure. Hi, babe
I gotta go find my other headphone. I said like a really good sandwich though
Thought I come up. I'm making some more more chapters of the second Omicron. How many chapters do I have?
I have this economic on now has 77 chapters. It's sped up until we catch up one hundred and forty six threads
Okay, it's growing
It's going like a little shop of horse plant, right? So we just look was recent ones on there. Okay
Shit, hold on
I'm really I'm really getting up there though like a lot of a lot of shows on there
Amazing. How are you guys doing? Yeah, this is mr. Rudy. Hi. I froze for a second. I'm sorry
Hi, hi. Oh Rudy
Rudy Rudy Rudy
You like oh you like it you like it when I rub your neck like that. Oh, oh that good
You love it, huh?
He loves it, right? Oh
But you'd run away if you didn't love you would you run away you wouldn't you wouldn't just sit on my lap
Hey more more more more. Okay
Yeah, but anyway, thank you always honor for coming on earlier. Yeah, I'm just I'm still building the second on the con
But I didn't have a picture of sweet peas late. I have her real picture actually you guys might be a little surprised. This is a real sweet pea
Maybe surprise it looks it's mainly though a voice changer can do isn't it these days
an old man can imitate a woman he's sweepy we all believe it's this woman but
it's a man the whole time yeah and he looks like that so there you go you know
sometimes you don't see their actual faces and it's like you know not obvious
that it's a real person you're gonna end up with a sweepy where you think it's
like you know I'm so sorry for the guys that hit on her you're hitting an old man
How many people we got here 23 how many psyche got watching him. I really good. I didn't really good lunch
I actually like they helped me. They're like, oh, you're still the other guys and we're off the same. Hey, my whole thing. Oh
Really good 13
Shout out to people that are part of the boycott. Oh, what are you doing here? Oh, that's right
No, you really have the numbers much up. Oh, thank you so much by the way for girl coming, you know
You're very sad sad people
People that are boycotting me and still here
Ridiculous as KK. You said rage quit. Well, there's KK on the front of it
I'll show you the real picture. It's okay. He loves salmon at one point. She loved him
Why are you saying I love KK as a thumbnail you fucking freak?
My god KK love salmon for
coming right up. I
Love him. Where is it?
This one oh
Oh, no, it's not that yes repost it. Oh, it's oh my god. Oh my god. No
Shared everywhere. Oh, that was the wrong one. I'm so sorry. Oh, I'm trying to take it off. Oh my god. Move. Oh my god. So sorry
That was the right one. I think it was
different one. Let me see
Well, I remember just that I love you on it. I
Got 24 watching
What is it here? He's got
Yeah, she had a nice rage quit by the way I can play my Easter special where she was on
I think she ended up rage quit on that one that's a rumble rage quit by the way. I'm not the Tommy James, but this is her
Sorry, here you go
Okay rumble tripp kick
Tripp I think loves me lately
Loves you by the way. He loves me
Yeah, we can replay here. We just played this stream earlier
He's gonna replay and what's in hope I can join our panel if she's serious. I will but I don't think she's serious
I need to hear out of her mouth, but here we go. Here's the same AKK
All those houses very special guest welcome gonna see her for a while. Hello
You literally just played this on his last live, I swear to fucking God
He literally just played this on his last life. He went to rumble and passed out playing this and now he's playing it again
Imagine fucking watching a clip of your own stream
Why are you live if you don't want to provide fucking entertainment? Don't go fucking live
This is weird as fuck
Weird
So you go live to play reruns and not even be there
How come a grown, how come a grown nickel has to tell you what to do with your stuff?
I live with my dad, papa.
No, is that why? Is that a real answer?
Well, that's okay. At least you're being honest for once.
God bless America, yeah.
Damn.
You can't tell the fucking truth.
He's a degenerate with an addiction to social...
fucking with me. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Mr. Ranger. Mr. Ranger. Oh, now you don't know who I live with, right?
I like that. Come on, bud. I mean, he says he loves you as dad, so whatever. I'm gonna run with that.
Tell it all. Oh, I'm waiting. Shout out to the iCloud. I got all my DMs back, baby.
I don't fucking care.
Yeah, I got all, tell it all. I've been waiting, bitch.
You're bummed.
All that stuff you talking about, juice, J and all of it up, you took all the money.
He took all his money, he's bummed big time.
Hell yeah, thank God, thank God, man.
I would take all that money too.
I would run all their pockets.
I'd run all their pockets.
Yeah, Brunsburg.
Good job.
I didn't even fucking say it.
I've hit it.
Fuck.
Oh no, it sounds like jealousy.
You sound jealous.
He, he's so fucking hard up.
He has to go to the back to the last time pre boycott that he had content
So that he has some content today
The boycott is hurting him so much he has to go and resort to reruns
The fact of the matter is
I'm restreaming him with 28 watching while he is
Sitting at 12 watching him shout out psyche. You're you're doing wonderful
Nobody wants to watch
Why you wanting to visit me after you visit about this character
I got the proof
But never forget. I had a black KK never forget. I had a black guy bitch
Probably she finally threatened you with actual action
You and that were all right.
All this, and he's got it.
You don't even live your life.
That's what it is.
You put all your stuff on repeat
scared that somebody's going to find out about you.
Who put pressure on the wishlist?
Who does that?
Why are you watching me?
Who put a bag of sofa on the wishlist?
He's afraid of his identity.
I don't know what you mean.
This is crazy.
At least she has someone else.
At least she has place to put a sofa.
At least she has the point of putting a sofa.
I doubt.
I bet you can't even put a sofa in your place if you want it.
Sounds like just hate or dog.
Hey Tommy, since you've been answering my questions, would you like to ask me where does he get his furniture from?
Can you ask him please?
Oh yeah, where do you get your furniture from, Bob?
This is his content.
Bob Lito.
And he's not even looking at his stuff.
Hey Bob Lito, Bob Lito, where do you get the furniture from?
Bob Lito.
On my box.
On my box, my box.
From your box.
Your box, there was something.
I'll keep going with that.
Do you even have room for a sofa?
Yeah.
Go ahead and tell us the truth.
Tell us what you thought.
I don't have to wash my ass.
I'll stop.
Oh my god.
Pick it.
You get to wash your ass.
I'll stop.
Oh my god.
How long do we have to wash our ass?
I'll stop.
Hey, we know you love Seat Stakes.
He's probably in this time to fix your mattress.
I'm gonna have to walk my ass.
Oh, sick.
You're sick, dude.
You're gross.
You're a garbage picker.
No, you're a garbage picker, bro.
What the fuck, dog?
Y'all, look.
Look it.
This is his stream earlier.
Checking in again.
OK?
He plays this clip
Now maybe it's not the clip with KK, I don't know but that's what he ended his show at playing a clip from looks like the same string
to he ends it goes live and
Now playing another
You're fucking on a big up air mattress. We are not the same. You pick garbage. Is that where you get your stinky love seat?
Recliner whatever you say.
Damn, especially in New York. Oh my god
Look at him, look at him go, look at him go, look at him go, look at him go, it's sad, it's go, oh my god.
I've never had to pick for a garbage thrift, stop this.
Can you imagine the scent in his little apartment between the two of them?
It's bad. It's bad. Oh my god.
This isn't even fucking content
Like it's not even like it was something good it's just a bunch of screeching and
Loudness I don't know it's not even
It's not even content fucking straight
garbage man my C no wait listen wait wait are you going to recap this garbage man are you going to recap this
community and how can you brand new Sam everybody money from over here
Sam man, Sam man are you Sam man
I'm talking the wish list is crazy wow
I don't stock them
well like beep beep at least watch like like other streams other than your own
go to like trip kick and play other shit or beep beep or pack yourself up but you're
reviewing shit that happened on your own panel
oh i'm sure he would love to have you q
Sure, he would love to have you. He's desperate for content right now
He somebody told him I was wanting him to join mine, which never happened
But he's like link Nancy and does she want me to join link to Kate's and I'll join no
I don't want you to fucking join my stream. I'm restreaming you you fucking moron
Come defend Sam and Zeus, come on, come save him.
I got you easy.
You told Zeus a lot, that's what he said.
Oh, he's a coward, you never join.
This dude's such a coward.
You told Zeus a lot, that's it.
He's such an obese coward.
Don't see that Tommy. He loves his team veggies. All right
I don't know what he thinks mind you his title was even KK agrees I'm a goat
Yikes, yikes, he literally went 10 minutes 730 reality Nancy commented to Jamie 740 he ended 10 fucking minutes without someone chatting in his fucking chat a psyche people don't want to watch reruns
They don't
They don't want to watch you watching something else
Even when I react to stuff like an I play clips I
Give my commentary throughout the clip. I don't just put a clip on
13 at one point was the most I saw 13 in chat while I have 27 on my backup channel
Psyche killed his career trying to be edgy by platforming a PDF bingo
Yeah, yeah, he was like somebody some trolling in there and said Kate wants you to join her panel and he got all hyped and kept
Asking for a link to my channel
Post the link I'll join post the link I'll join
He was so geeked up
We win
Well, like even if you're going to play clips you have to talk why do I have to teach you shit psyche?
No, I don't think he did I think he literally um
Bebe I think he he was
discourage that 10 minutes went by and no one chatted in his chat and he right
quit is my opinion because he gets so butt-hurt so butt-hurt when people don't
chat in his chat well you have to give them something to chat about and putting
People aren't gonna chat. We already all saw this not to mention people were in my chat chatting. Oh
I'm sure he will be live again soon. Um, I'll
Stay live for a little bit. We'll watch to see if he
If he comes back or not
Sike you since you don't have any viewers left. You might as well go look for your fucking cat. It's not dead already
He's probably waiting for Kate to end the restream. Oh, I'm sure
I'm sure I'll just go live again
Even if I can't like if I'm busy like I was just about ready to go take you guys down and
As soon as I got enough charge on my battery and I was just gonna go clean the kitchen while I restrain them
Like fuck it. I'll put myself on mute and get some shit done
Unless the cat has some McDonald's he won't care facts
Talk about making every single wrong move as a panel streamer everything everything
Now the the okay if he turns on Brandon Q
What do you guys want to get get like how many people do you think people will?
instantly go back I
Won't I'm done. He showed me who he is
He can denounce Brandon Q all day every day. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done
But I think a certain amount of people will thing that is thing. That is if you're out there. I'm disappointed in you
I'm disappointed in you
Be the got done today can he ran right over into fucking um
In the psychics chat
He won't unless Alex does yeah true
You think Michael Christine for sure Christine the flip-flopper. I don't I don't know about Brownsburg
He's saving other cats with his rat's nest to feed on you basically saving a family
Yeah, somehow he's ended up with additional cats he claims. I don't get that
I don't ever go there before I find him boring even before brandon q. He is boring
As far as I'm concerned he's no longer providing content and became the content a while ago. Yeah pretty much
Hello crystal
Hello
Yeah, Christine inserting herself, but and then I had to laugh because Mimi went live
Tagging fucking Karen after that. So it really did no good
I don't know why but that shit made me laugh I saw Mimi went live and I saw that she take care
I was like, oh well Mimi said fuck y'all. I want to smoke
I don't give a fuck about what any of you warned me bring that ass here Karen. I want all this smoke.
Mimi, even real, I'm starting to think is just AI.
Oh, Mimi is real.
Did you guys see my new, my AI today?
Oh, where is it?
Oh, here it is.
Somebody take away my chat, G-B-T.
Someone take it away.
That was her crystal today because Rita did so much crying
We have lives in the middle of the light and of the night. We have lives today
She is really she's really upset with you there
Crystal crystal got a crush. Do you think?
You think so who's crystal got a crush on?
Sorry
Take a wild guess
Crystal loves me. Whoa. I think I think you must be
Meaning Q Chris. Oh, you got a crush on Q
Like a
Hey Nicole
I was just here re streaming psyche, but he rage quit. Is he live again yet?
Oh, that shit was funny. 23 minutes and 16 seconds that lasted.
Crystal said he called me baby girl. Oh.
We got names for each other already. Hey. Hey. Hey. I can't believe I got 52 here on my backup channel for a
re-stream. I wasn't even planning on... Now I feel bad. I feel like I got to stay live. Y'all are here. Fuck.
Must be a boring night. I'm on the backup channel with 52 people. What in the hell?
Re-stream the rage that he rage quit, right?
I can't, I can't believe we quit.
He said at seven, okay, so some 730 reality Nancy commented 736 like he said link Nancy and does she want you to join 737 he says Luke to Kate and I'll join 739 he says okay never mind then at 740 he ended.
W, W, W. Here's the two psyche boycott images I made today.
Well, AI made for me.
Here's one.
Just type in here, Psyche.
We know you're watching.
I'm not going to ban you, Psyche.
It's okay
That's one
You think he has a better chance with barb I barb is feeling her some Q
She is
Hey swan man
Then here's the other one,
which is my thumbnail.
Why isn't it showing up?
That's weird.
I shared this one, everyone.
It's like I'm missing poster.
Everyone share it if you see it.
You can feel free to repost on your tabs.
Sorry about that. Sorry about that. You guys want to let's see um
Here's a puppy update look at the babies
Look at the seepin babies
The baby
Mine is the one laying on his back this belly up
Well, my parents, but it's mine
I steal them stealing them. I'm stealing him. I just love all the poise goggles
Anyways, I don't know what else to talk about I got y'all here
I hate to kidnap you. They're um cock-a-poo's
The mom is a cock-a-poo and the dad is a poodle so more poodle than cocker spaniel
Yeah, the one in the middle here, I'm let me see if I got another one of them the name is tentatively Benji
I don't have one on the computer that, well, I have one, but I don't want to dox three years.
Right?
So sweet.
I'm so excited.
Otherwise, it's going to be a problem because she loves going to grandma and papa's house and
If she don't get along with the baby, she won't be going to grandma and papa's house. So
Can you show some goat versus eagle action on your channel what goat versus eagle action
Hi, Barry. Good evening sunshine. You found us. I
was restreaming
psyche for the boycott, but um
He rage quit so now we're just hanging out for the moment. Oh
Chef beat up
Why you suck and beat us fucking Harry Bush
I would ask cars
They just need to be introduced each other's spaces slowly over time. Yeah, I'm afraid Lola is gonna be
Gonna have her feelings hurt a little bit, but she'll she'll do okay
I think she'll do okay with it being a baby. She'll I'm hoping she'll mother him
It's a thing war. No, I don't want to see goats and
And fucking eagles at war
The spectra of
Oh
It's the ghost of Barry. I know somebody asked me today if Barry was dead or alive. I was like, I'm not sure his status today
I don't know. I don't know what he is
You dead or alive homie
Hey leave Tracy alone I
Dropped the link, but I know the only person that wants to take the link is not allowed up here, so
Um, and it is not because of Barry. Just FYI
It is your own
Stupidity and blatant racism that doesn't kill
Like at first I thought you were just like
Edgy using the but you really do hate black people and I've realized that so I'm I'm really good on that. Oh
Crystal you want to join?
Hold on a moment
Hold on a second I might have a special guest I don't get it. I I do get it. I do get that you're um
I don't I don't feel like his hatred towards black people is banter. I feel like he really does
Hate black people
It's called triggering sneaker sniffers so
Being racist is just an offending an entire group of people
Trigger just a few I
Don't get that
And most of the ETC isn't even black so I really
Like most of them aren't black most of them are no they is not black salmon ain't black
Nor does I mean the only reason Sam and gets triggered by that word is because he knows that it'll um
Get him clapped. He wouldn't
Here you don't like black people. I'm with Kate on that one, but I let you on panels because I let you be Q
Doesn't mean I agree with you. Yeah. Well, um me letting someone I mean
Yeah, I don't
I'm good on that
Barry is black Barry is black
Especially in the pants if you know what I mean
Yeah fuck bigots amen Timmy time two times Timmy James
i have no problem pow wowing with you on other panels are you sure about that because i'm pretty
sure i ended up leaving crystal's panel last night because of you so
you get to be too much sometimes skew and you were it wasn't even because you were
Well, I thought we were going to have a special guest, but hold on, we'll see.
Why do you keep sending question marks crystal or can I just not see the emote I
Know there's no link dropped
Oh there he is
You talking to me?
Hi.
What's up?
Welcome.
I let you right on up.
I didn't give you no intro.
I didn't make you wait.
Boom.
Let you up.
Hold on.
I'm doing something.
I got to set my shit up for some reason.
My sound and shit weren't working.
So I had to fucking do a different browser.
Hold on.
Yeah, I wanted my bad. I wanted to talk about that motherfucking beta cook man. She cooked this shit out of crystal man
She cooked her ass so bad. She was a complexion of fucking duchy man. She cooked this shit out of her
Like be the beat is like top five for female cookers in this sector
Like she cooked this shit out of crystal like crystal like crystal can't come back from that cook like she cooked this shit out of her
Hey crystal, I fuck with you, but she cooked she cooked the shit out of you man
I say beta like I put I put Shannon Shannon is number one, of course
I put trolla uh two
I put uh cake three
No, I put I put boston three
I put Kate for and I put a I put B to five for female cookers
Like like crystal crystal, you you know where you you not even in the top 10 crystals like she cooked it sit out of you man
But you need to find a way to figure out how to cook
Because I don't think you can come back from that cook she cooked it sit out of the crystal
I'm telling you crystal everybody seen it. Did you play the clip already of her getting cooked? You didn't play that clip
Did you come on? I play that clip. Yeah, ain't that a big clip?
psyche. Hey man, fuck him man. Nobody don't give a fuck about him man. Fuck him
He ain't even he's not even live. So what the fuck is you waiting on? You're not doing shit right now play that fucking cook, man
Damn people probably think I'm just imagining shit man. Let's say Crystal here right now
Crystal probably didn't see the cook like she could just take notes just a crystal just sit back and take notes
Be the cook this shit out of you. You said she couldn't hold an audience. She she showed you that she that she had an audience man
That's what I like man
I like to see when people go back and forth and they cook this shit out of somebody that's they enemy
That's what she did man. It's just like straight cook
Like she didn't she didn't have to play no songs. She just got right into it and just cook this shit out of your ass
She cooked you man. If fucking Kate hurry up and fucking play this shit. There we go Salusa pack yourself up
She cooked this shit out of your ass crystal
Who struck you that was Alex to be fair
They I don't even fuck with be the but I say be to be cooking man when be the one to cook so you can cook
I'm telling you
That's one of my protease
Produce by the way good you you you my protease. Oh
I'm like be the protease to lose the chicken cakes
I take I take a lot of females underneath my wing
They say Chris crystal I tried to help her but she don't want to listen I got I can't be dealing with people with females that
I want to listen
They say Kate already know
But it was a time when Kate was hanging on it was hanging on the ledge
Whatever I see lucky that I'm up here
Like a lot of shit and then I see I've seen something I can't remember if it was crystal playing something
Somebody was playing the homeless king and queen
Content of something and they was talking about fucking proofing shit
Like why the fuck is they saying the same shit that I've been saying?
Like all they doing is saying the same the same repeat shit that I'm saying about fucking
Fuckin the homeless king and queen was up there saying something about proof it and not showing proof and why should they show proof when
When they don't matter and shit like that like I've been saying that shit
It's all they doing is copying the same shit. I've been saying who's the homeless king and queen the motherfuckers living in the fucking attic damn. Oh
Shit, I don't watch them. I don't know what they were you hot. Is you hot?
I'm sad. Who else is the homeless king and queen around here?
Huh, let's talk about cubie and homeless. So I didn't know but who is his queen? He don't have a queen. No, I don't know
man
Hey, hey, like like what is what is you doing? Is you distracted?
Yeah, I am
Damn
Okay, well just play to pack yourself up man. So people can see fucking uh crystal get her ass cooked
I'm not gonna have no choice but to cover this.
There. Hey, guys. Hi. Hi. I'm back. It's 1 a.m. here. I see 16 people. Oh, God, I'm trying
to get some fucking sleep, but oh my God, today is I'm telling you guys, this people
I am so like fed off of this fucking dumbass people that lie over and over on my fucking name.
And then you've got a bunch of people sitting there and instead of fucking saying, you know what?
Like a show proof or whatever, they just go with it.
Fuck you, Crystal Anne.
You're sitting there saying that I fucking told you that I was attracted to fucking Cheeto.
And while you were like, he was trying to kiss you, he mentioned you're a fucking weird ass.
Disgusting!
fucking liar. All of you guys that get my name mixed up in the middle of your stupid like fucking
Drama queen bullshit because you have nothing better to do
You're gonna get your fucking turn because I got a lot of fucking proof for your fucking ass next time you talk
You better come with fucking proof because I'll tell you something me and cheeto are still really good friends
And we keep in contact and we've had this conversation several times
Because he's asked me to fucking stream with him and I'm like no because people have made up
And it's like in a group of people like stream
We're gonna be doing this and that and I have proof where he's like people are
Tell me who's talking shit because
Disgusting
Hovered it fucking whore of fucking crystal and that's where we go
It's starting with every fucking streamer that you could ever imagine and you could think of has the fucking nerve to sit here
And fucking make up lies about me. I've never been with one fucking guy online
Physically, I've never fucking had any kind of like I'm looking at us anything like that
Hort fucking
He's sit there and you spread your legs
Or a fucking Mary
Pleasure you are a weirdo chicken Andy you fucking sit here with your upside down fucking lives and lie on my fucking name
Saying that I didn't fucking I don't have a bachelor's money on it. How much you want to bet?
You fucking skank ass whore don't ever fucking mention your my my name should not be coming out of your fucking mouth
Because I will fucking lay out shit with fucking receipt and you'll sit there and you'll fucking cry
Let's talk about your fucking boyfriend who takes 10 fucking clonopens a date
Coming straight out of his fucking mouth. You fucking junky bitch
Just because you're sitting there in your second topping pill it doesn't make you fucking not a fucking druggy you fucking bitch
Don't ever talk about your trim it all beta makeup lies about my fucking life
Not one of you can fucking prove that not fucking once
she's disgusting fucking trying to get me mixed up with fucking shit I don't want to be involved with
just because you got your ass fucking like bit by fucking Karen once again
and I've been fucking like telling you stay the fuck away from me and that shenanigan
you're blaming it on me don't fucking talk about me and everybody else that sits there and tries to
use my name to you know vent out or whatever this and that you guys stick in your own fucking
Listen to me fucking crystal and you have the worst fucking reputation you lie more than anybody else
I've ever fucking seen you have called the police on fucking people like including fucking
Friends with Bruno Gamble everybody you fucking are a weirdo. Nothing about you has fucking changed
Don't sit there and fucking lie on my fucking name. You skank ass whore now. Let's talk about your fucking boyfriend
You're still called boyfriends
Two that you've had in the past couple one the one that you called the police on and sent me fucking pictures of him
Out there. Oh my god
You know, he's trying to get in my dad doesn't want him in because he's a junkie and he doesn't hasn't paid rent
And he just wants to stay at my house. Bitch. You're not a fucking queen
You collect fucking junkies and fucking some bad
Every guy you've ever fucking been with is a fucking junkie from the streamers to the people that you
You fucking pick look at the fucking Jesus guy you're with the other guy that you fucking call the police on you fucking retarded
Bitch, why don't you tell everybody why you got kicked out of the military you fucking scumbag don't talk on my fucking name
You understand that hold on
This is me
Beat us kiddies by myself 65 people clicking your motherfucking ass. You sit there and you say
Whiskers out you declawed your fucking cat
Two years ago a year ago. Why for your fucking furniture you selfish disgusting animal abuser
You fucking declaw your fucking cat because you don't want to ruin your fucking furniture. I'll pay you a hundred dollars right now
What did you do to them?
You had them declawed you selfish fucking bitch. That's against the law and most fucking like most of the states except the fucking
Getter is correct about that. You fucking live in there and clean beta. I'm kitty gang. I made you shut the fuck up
Pazza shut the fuck up. All right. Don't fucking mention my name. Don't talk about me in any fucking manner that you know nothing
about come with fucking receipts or get the fuck out of here. That's all I wanted to tell you
I'm going to drop the link for anybody that wants to come up for a second.
We do have Lady B in the chat.
Lady B knows about the Claw of Cats.
And you know what?
That's you guys' project to ask me.
Go ahead.
Tell her to show her fucking cats claws.
She had her fucking cats.
She just told me this.
There we go.
Lady B said it.
It was one of the most disgusting things that I've ever fucking heard.
Highlight Lady B.
Highlight Lady B, please.
Took me two weeks to get it out of my brain and I can I think her cat is the most adorable thing
But I can't even barely look at her cat without thinking what she fucking did to the fucking cat
So don't sit here fair. Tell me I'm the real beat. I didn't realize that it was cruel
It's not illegal here and a lot of people do it. So I had no idea
I had to look it up to plus trolling. She covered this clip and I
Think she she asked Google somebody and they said it is cruel
So and plus a lady B said it so it is cruel if she is doing it
I don't know for sure, but I'm saying that's what be the suit
Tell me you learn something every day because I didn't know
That's how I don't have cats or dogs
Yeah, I don't I don't know nothing about cats. I just know people do it. So no it is it is cruel
It is cruel you say you can Google it to too cool for school just Google it
Man plus lady B. She knows so and she said it
Not sure when it come to animals. I trust lady B
Yeah
You like shitty gay or I'm the shitty gang or I created it. What the fuck you're nothing
What did you create? Are you carter verse? Are you crystal verse? Are you fucking yapety-yap verse?
You're an animal abuser you fucking
Because I don't want to rain my furniture I challenge you to show the fucking claws
Push the little paw and see if it comes out. You fucking lying bitch saying that I pull my fucking cats whiskers out
Shut your fucking mouth
Don't talk about my exes. I'll talk about your fucking exes
Don't talk about the guys that you think I was with on the line, or I will fucking list every fucking
scumbag that you fucking were in
Garbage hotel, I've never had one fucking streamer in my fucking house
We have the audacity to sit there and say that I fucking did anything you I blew captain content
Shut the fuck up. You sat there and you took a picture of fucking chicken Andy when he was sleeping like a fucking
Cycle Jody areas to like prove that you fuck this guy. You fucking weirdo
I'll fucking cook you all day long. I've been fucking dealing with your shit fucking long enough
Do not associate me with the fucking Carter verse or Sharon or any of your fucking shenanigans
Hey Mimi. What's up?
I was over there when the conversation happened, when it was mentioned, and I said that that's not true.
I told all of them that that's not true.
Over and over again.
All fairness Mimi, you don't know you weren't there.
but I mean absolutely everybody that knows I did a couple of streams and not one time there's any
interaction between me and him like that it's because everybody else can stream they can go to
RVs they can all hang out with different age groups they can have people at their house they can do
whatever but me streaming with a group of people I ended up blowing the person I ended up having
sex with them I was with the under you she's a fucking scumbag and I'm sorry you know I don't
than any of this shit but if anything got blown out of proportion is because
that's what she fucking does. That's what she fucking does. As far as like Karen
and INX and all that shit goes I I have been doing streams for like a year and a
Barely that woman ever came up until Crystal came around and brought her on my
It's not good. Oh Karen wants us or Karen is attacking me or as I ignore her block her
We all said ignore ignore up and sticking to it
Not one fucking conversation with the lady and you sit there and you negotiate with her back and forth
And then two three days later you find out oh, it's to your bed of like disadvantage
uh link up with people like Ziya and other people to make other people mad get the fuck out of here
you fucking weirdo ass fucking bitch you know what if whatever Mimi did it was one person
that she you know Mimi has known him for a very long time and you know what if she did do that
or she didn't do that she's nothing compared to somebody like Prisco I'll name how many streamers
What's my body count five and none of them are fucking from the internet not one
It could have been it might have been and I'm not like fucking hating on it
But goddamn for you to sit here and fucking accuse me of being with people when you fucking like fuck the bunch of fucking dudes from
Every fucking guy has all, no, there is nobody, no one for them that's not critical and said
they have a great experience as a friend and think they don't know what they should do.
that she talks shit about everybody. And then later on, oh, we're fine. Because we need to
fucking hate on keep my fucking name out of your fucking mouth. I don't give a fuck about you. I
don't give a fuck about the stupid carniverse people barbs, fucking cricket ass fucking mouth
who fucking borrowed money from me. This lady has the audacity to act like she's luxury, but she
couldn't fucking give enough five or $10 in her pocket every fucking week, take money from me to
streamers, shut the fuck up, you petty ass bitches. Don't even let me open this fucking
counter-worn. Alright? And everything I have proof for it.
So Mimi I see you said you were gonna go live or something. I told you I gotta vet my shit out
I'm not gonna let have like some fucking bitch
Guys dick that I didn't when I have like actual screenshots and receipts and proof that these guys like I mean who the fuck is saying that shit
It's never happened. I'm not fucking tree not golden. You've done fucking bitch
Sorry
No, you're good
Well, yeah, you've got to vent yourself out, you know, I
Again as far as like the Christine and all that shit. I mean, I think you got blown out of the proportion
But I
I mean, I'm telling you we got people that are covering so many panels about this brand and choose day
uh a crystal uh fucking cake that how the fuck am i the one to inform anybody everybody already
knows what's going on i don't need to tell anybody anything and i haven't even had time to fucking
talk to nini i didn't even know that she would even be involved or ever intertwined in this
Anyways, yeah, I just wanted to come up really, you know, really, really fast.
Thank you for coming up with me. I know you got to go and do your thing. I'll listen.
I literally, I was like so tired, I lost my sleep.
It's like so fucked up to sit here
and like here lies after lies about you, you know?
I support almost everybody, you know?
I'm like, okay, go to this person's channel,
go to this, all of my, all of my,
I did it even with, with Crystal.
Like that was the thing, what she literally was like,
how do I do this and this and that?
And like, okay, teacher like kind of the ropes.
And then she was, okay, oh, everybody come to my safe place.
Okay, do it, but at least when you go there,
don't talk shit about me.
Just be grateful that I even like, you know,
I don't know I let you bring that fucking bullshit drama because I barely ever have to deal with Karen
I don't talk to them. I would get three-way calls and I'm like who's on the line
I don't want to talk to Karen. I really don't and I've tried to talk to her
I've tried to get her like for years to calm down and be a better person and she made these fake promises and it never worked
So I gave up wait months and months ago
Crystal just gave up three days ago because of Brandon Q and other people figure that one out
Thank you, MFW. I thank you for the sweet message too. I saw that earlier
Yeah, there is no link. I mean, it's kind of late. I'm about
What crystal? Well, I don't think lying about people is winning
I don't think being a total fucking lunatic that oh, you know what else she said
She said that I made up a rumor about her getting 51 50. That's not true. That was Barb
I stood up for her. I played people know this. These are these are actually on lives, you know, I was like, no, she did it
Fuck crystal. She never did that. She never got 51 50 with Barb that made it up
But it's so convenient for crystal and to fucking lie and that's a one
That's a W just because you fucking lie. That's disgusting. Enjoy that thing
But I wanted to come up really live and bent out. I mean really fast live and bent out
Like what just suggest a little bit of what's going on anybody wants like cool for a seed
I will provide it. I will tell you
You come with fucking receipts when you talk shit about
So crystal you couldn't even stick around to defend yourself. You had to go fire up promote your live here and then go fire up alive
Yikes
Then
And keep my fucking name out of your fucking downward fish mouth fucking mouth
I don't like you crystal and you're a fucking liar. I don't fuck with liars
Yeah, go live crystal and you go right ahead and go with her Q. Goodbye
Damn
Like what what Chris was just not seeing that I
Don't know
And then you respect you respect to her and when you when you went live you didn't mention in her chat
No, and she's done this to me multiple times now
Yeah, you gotta say something you gotta put your foot down man. You can't let me
I went live and she came up said she was live and
then proceeded to
Say she was going live again and she'd be over in her chat where Q could be
Like she don't know like that's what that's what I don't get like a lot of people is sitting up there
Like they point the finger at this person because they don't like them
But then like she don't know the story that QB fucking spitting on women
He'd be spitting on fucking bitches and shit. That's fucking assault knows. You don't care. That's what I'm saying
So how you gonna say how you gonna fucking?
Talk shit about fucking branding Q and fucking gay and shit, but you fucking with fucking Q and shit
She knows she says she doesn't care. That's what I'm saying. So people pick and choose
So don't fucking sit up there and act like you champion for this fucking person
Or you got an issue with this person when the person you rocking with just as bad as that person
Like get the fuck out of here man, that's what I'm saying people it's just fucking selective outrage
That's why I'm be paying attention to that shit
Irritated the fuck out of me
Hmm
When the when the what they say when the grass is cut the snakes of show
Yeah, pretty much I
Don't see I don't see why you don't listen to me man. I told you about people man. You don't want to listen I
Can own I can only lead you to water Kate that can't help you drink it
So obviously obviously she didn't see the cook so like I just wanted people because I guess a lot of people not served up to
Pack yourself up. I've been promoting the dude for like two weeks
You've been dropping his links and everything, but I guess people didn't see that so only thing
I wanted I wanted people to be able to check the clip out and here would be to have this
She couldn't watch the clip. She was live entertaining Q all day. No, well, they they dayton
I don't know
What you call it, but so I mean so what be this is what be the saying is is correct as beta said her fucking
Her place her door is she got like a revolving door and shit with streamer dudes like a lot of dudes
No, I think she used to be that way not anymore. Oh
So she used to be a whore
No, I'm saying she used to like be around a bunch of streamers and shit, but yeah, but be the same as she was fucking them all
Yeah, that's what be the was talking about in that clip that she was fucking a lot of streamer guys
So like if you a streamer, then I guess you got like full access to that pussy
So I mean, I'm a streamer I consider myself a streamer
So Chris crystal crystal. I'm I consider myself a streamer
Cuz I have stream I have like I have did a little bit of streaming
So I mean I consider myself a streamer. So Chris. I'm just putting that out there. I am a streamer
Salute to the chat chicken cakes a berry blue
What is that chairman worth a piece of shit because you're so friends with Karen? Oh, I'm not friends with Karen
I talked to Karen in like a week. I don't fuck with here. I say that's what I'm saying
She got she got information fucked up. I ain't sorry. I talked to Karen in a week
Because Karen got a new number she so she haven't hit me up on her new number
So she was hitting me up on IG and I just stopped reading her shit
Self-projective salutes, but you watching that you watch her live you might as well play as part of it
You might as well play it you was playing a psych shit
Just a this ain't that what the backup channel for salute the blogger
I might as well since she promoted it here fuck that shit irritated me like she could easily taken my Lincoln defended herself
Told her she can have the link and she could come up when it was done
I just wanted to get the clip through if we let her up. We'd never get finished with the clip
But not only does she promote it
like
How many how many people in the chat after that after that y'all heard that clip that y'all think be the cook their ass
That they be the cook there
I mean, you know, you probably don't think so because you don't like her. I mean, I don't like be the either
But I mean to me she cooked her
Cuz I mean when Chris Crystal really don't do no cooking all she do is just play like play other people clips and shit
She really don't be saying shit about her
She don't even she don't even do that, right? Yeah. Yeah, he up there right away. That's why I told Kate man. Don't trust that dude
I mean, I've been telling Kate for the longest don't trust that guy, but she keep fucking with
So many times I'm gonna tell you before I just let you get burned
She says she didn't see it okay in so we showed it all you had to do was wait like if you got alive going wise you over here chatting
All you had to do was just wait because people wanted to hear the clip before you came up here and defended yourself
The lake was gonna get dropped you couldn't wait uh 15 how long was that clip 15 minutes?
I dropped it as soon as the thing was done like when did that clip come out that clip came out like early this morning
So I mean you had all day like I've been promoting the dude for two weeks, uh, crystal
You now serve up to pack yourself up
Dr. Can you drop the link, uh, please so she can serve up
Oh the link to pack yourself up. Yeah
I've been sharing this shit out. That's what I'm saying. We've been we've been promoting them for two weeks
Oh, but I say when crystal got up here all she's gonna do is just talking and one gonna let the clip finish
We just want to get the clip out of the way
Then once the clip was finished, she could have fucking dog this shit out of beta
I say we don't we don't neither one of us up here give a fuck about beta I
Said I just thought that she cooked the shit out of her
Yeah, I didn't I told her she could come up when it was done. I didn't have the link publicly posted until
The clip was almost done and obviously she wouldn't have seen it because if she hadn't seen it yet
She wouldn't she wouldn't go see it because I guess nobody told her about it
But I don't know how trolley got a hold of it because trolley played it on her shit
That's when trolley was looking up the fucking the the claw on the cat because I didn't know I thought it was a regular procedure
Yeah, I didn't realize that it was like
Not
Was frowned upon it's not illegal here and people do it here all the time so
But I mean what like what's the point but I mean I understand what the furniture and shit
But still like why would you even just get a cat there? If you know if you know cat get claws
I mean, I said if I had a cat I would do rubber tips for his cats
Who?
My son has these little rubber tips that go on the cats claws
Oh, yeah, I'm not doing all that. I like that. I would just I would I just wouldn't get a leather couch
I would just get like a regular fabric couch
That's the only thing you really got to worry about the claws for ain't it is the furniture
Yeah, or like yourself I guess
Yeah, but I mean that's what I that's what I'm saying if you get a cat you I mean that's something you should already be prepared for
No, I don't know shit about
They still yeah, they still claw with cloth they'll tear the shit up, but that's why you get like scratching posts and
Shit like that like places for them to scratch
Man, I haven't played my call of duty probably about a week or so. He said Barry's excited today boy. He got the Terry
There every time I every time I get on my fucking system and shit
It's always a fucking update like every time I if I'm not on that if I'm not on that thing for like a couple days
Every time I get on it. It's always a fucking update either fucking
Sony got an update or call of duty got an update and that should be taking hours. I'd be like fuck this
End up not even playing
Make sure y'all hit that like button just the backup that just a backup channel. Yeah, I didn't even get a notification
I was just watching some sour X shit and then I seen it pop up that you was love
Yeah, it was just it was just a restream psyche. It was funny. We had like 20 some people in here
Almost 30 people and like 12 watching
And no one was chatting no one chatted for like 10 minutes and so he rage quit
No, he should have been he should have been prepared for it. That's his fault. I
Said well fucking don't listen well, but didn't he do the same shit with LD though
What double down and it was an L was an LD or KZ one of them he was because he was still having KZ on this panel
LD he did it too. LD still comes on this panel. That's what I'm saying. So is this
Like it's nothing new with that guy. He been doing it, but Brandon Q. I think
The area you don't consider LD and Brandon Q the same. No, I think Brandon Q is way worse
There's way more evidence than like
like stuff like that against Brandon in my opinion where I can like LD
They well they can't show it because it's child porn. So like or it has you know underage nudity
So that's why no one shows the proof of LD because the girl was 15
And who's gonna keep a 15 year old?
nude in their phone for proof
Oh, yeah, yeah, you go to you go to prison for that, right? So that's why there is so I get why there isn't proof for him
But like with with Brandon, it's just way more stuff out there
And I think Brandon is more of a danger to society and I don't know why you too fucking
Maybe cuz maybe cuz he tagged me but for some reason they fucking recommended his fucking channel and shit
Boom Brandon Q's
Damn
But that's what I'm saying, I don't know cuz it might have been cuz he tagged us in that pose
I don't remember but I don't know why they fucking
Fucking recommended him. I fucking did not interest it
Hell yeah
I recommend this channel
Hey, Shane Adams
Yeah, modern warfare 2 is when I when I got introduced to Carla duty that was that was the best game
I used to fucking a new world. What did they call it a the new tube? I used to do that shit all the time
motherfuckers used to hate that shit like
Gears of war and shit that was my game and then somebody introduced me to Carla duty
And then I started playing that shit. I say modern warfare 2. I had a crew man shit. I love that guy
That's when that's when I was when I use my headset after that. I stopped using my headset
Oh, you can read that
You know how Alex and thank you love to run stuff through AI to analyze it run the brandy Q video through AI and
It's analysis of him as wild. What do you do upload the transcript? I don't know how they do that or do you just
I um
Today explained the whole CPS paperwork PEPS thing to AI to ask if it was illegal.
They said no, the chance, if anything, there could be civil action, but since the paperwork
wasn't obtained illegally, like no one broke into a system to get it since the person who
And it was about, you know, like, it was her paperwork and she gave it to Granny.
There's really, there's no laws that were broken.
But yeah, I did a whole analysis of that.
I felt like a retard explaining all this shit to AI.
Well, there was this girl, she gave her paperwork.
Pebs is just um, I honestly don't think civilly she could she could sue her she could absolutely sue her
But there is not a criminal. There's not a law that was broken
Because I think I think I don't know I don't think I don't know I think pebs is um
I think a lot of that dumbness. I think she does for for play. I
Don't think she has done me. She tried to come on
That's what she says is just too stupid you leaving trip have a good night
To lose the trip be safe
Yeah, I
Don't I say I think she just like goofy and she just think it's funny to be that stupid
Maybe please dumb to lose to Anita
Yeah, I agree Samantha. She may not be as dumb as she acts but she's still dumb. Yeah. Yeah. She's still dumb as hell
But I don't think she is dumb. I don't I don't think she's done with it Sam Sam, man
I don't think she's done with him
Like when it comes to the animal shit, he might have her on that but I don't think I don't think that she's done with him
Hell yeah, I asked an AI
I was just curious
Because I don't know how to like what law it would be. So I just was like explain
He said crystal dis and me hey wire
Yeah, should we play it? Yeah, I wanted to hear
Not fucking right now and you're a piece of shit, too because you're still friends with fucking Aaron
And imagine going over and kissing Vita's ass
Imagine that Vita called she helped call CPS on Trisha. Oh, but Vita cooked me, right?
Right. Oh
Vita's friend
And threaten to have clubs at my parents, but Vita is this good person, right? No
I'm upset with you because she's like you fucking bitch fucking promoted you're live and then
Um, I never called her a bitch and I'm not extremely upset Q way to go and fucking lie and make shit
Sound way worse than what it was
Yeah, hold on. I break back
Yikes Q you're fucked up went and left the stream. Yeah
I just wanted to say one thing about that situation.
Kate, you might be mad at me for being racist,
but I never did anything near what Barry did to you.
He fucking exposed your nudes.
He fucking, he exposed videos of you crying
on Discord.
So you might you might be mad at me for saying the n-word, but I never did as much emotional damage as to you as the person
That's on your panel right now. Think about that. Why are you trying to drag me in with Kate? I didn't I don't have an issue
I'm not dragging you in with nothing
Myself and I'm gonna talk. Oh, she's talking shit. I was just letting you she's talking shit. She's not a she's not
I doubt she's talking shit. Why would she? Oh, I promise you I'll put it on my mother's life
I was just there. I was just talking by the way
Because I was disgruntled that she advertised her live and went over there. I don't think that's talking back and rewind three minutes
Go back to go to her stream and rewind three minutes
talking to imagine being a middle-aged adult is concerned about what other adult is doing and saying
and where they're hanging out you must really have a shallow life what are you talking about
this is the internet i'm here to uh fucking talk shit i don't care really at the end of the day
Who's where I want to know why do people think beta cooked me because I'm a grown-ass woman 37 not reacting to her
Like she's the disgusting slut online and everyone knows that she's the one that's an alcoholic
Oh my eggs my eggs, but I'm friends with that sober now. Congratulations. I got him sober, right?
People can talk shit all they want on me. I don't give a fuck. That's the difference between me and beta beta
You don't want this war with Bruno. And by the way, it's UFC night
So he's watching UFC and as far as my man goes he has more of a degree than you ever will get
That's for sure. And for you to even drag my man into this when you put your fiance out there like that is disgusting
Okay, let's not forget about Katie. Okay, beta. You have what?
Let's be honest your whole family hates you was cute talking because I didn't hear cute
don't understand why people they think oh let me just go let be be the ones
talk shit on curse let's just go and take her side do it do it no one took
you to side I don't think that's the kind of person she is beta the fact that
you're still talking to Cheeto is fucking wild I talked to no IPT really to be
honest none of them
I'm gonna speed this back so many people still hate you. Why because you're a piece of shit
Imagine that imagine Dawson people imagine being a porn spreader
imagine that I
Got to get to flying fucks y'all want Vita. I'll leave the internet. Why I don't give a fuck
No, I'll be on the internet for Q and Vita
But as far or and bar where we have normal conversation
And what exactly are you doing?
What exactly are you doing?
But you're here as well
Right, exactly. What are you are doing the same thing? Let me help you out. Why don't you go somewhere else and write your paragraphs?
Okay, no one cares
Imagine if it's if it's if we're all doing it. What are you doing?
And crystal I don't I mean, I'm sure you're on with your own string
The only thing that bothered me was that you promoted your own string here
I didn't call you a bitch. I didn't say anything negative about you
I don't think Barry was taking Bita's side.
I don't think she gets that.
Barry's not taking her side, so to speak.
He's just saying she cooked you.
He don't fuck with Bita,
but I'm glad Barry got me all involved in this
and then left me.
Sations.
But as far as I'm concerned Vita's a washed up 51 year old who can't even fucking get a boyfriend of herself like it's fucking weird
She wants to put blame on me and do all this shit talking your true colors will show and
People will turn on you again
Because unlike you, I don't need the fucking internet
She used our G the other day as a threat, but watch and see what happens. Yeah called the cops on me
If you want to go to this border, I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a fuck.
Because what will happen is she'll still get exposed.
I'm down to have regular conversations
with regular human beings.
I don't give a fuck about trolling.
I don't give a fuck about mentally ill people.
And Abita wants to try and sugar me
it's not gonna work.
I'm not the same Crystal Ann from years ago.
Oh and bride my friend. She knows exactly what went down all my timelines when it comes to relationships. Thank you very much. I've had
Imagine
Me helping the guy get sober and I'm friends with that person, right? But the man I'm currently with has nothing to do with anything
He doesn't do drugs. He doesn't drink. He's not as freaking sloppy as bitch like you beta and you're jealous of that
People actually yeah, it's sped up. Do you want me to speed it up more what comes out of beta's mouth?
I don't give a fuck it's not illegal to declaw and if people want to hate me on that cool hate me
I don't give a fuck. It's not your animal. It's not your life. I cat loves me
Using it needs sped up more and another thing is
Imagine being 51 years old an internet drama
Imagine going after me who have who really doesn't give two flying fucks about you beta
I don't care if you want to go and I don't care get hit by a bus. I don't care
No, we can speed it up more
I just want to get it because I don't care to listen to stupid shit about me. I don't I
Know my life and I know my truth and that's all that fucking matters
Okay, why are you bringing X's of mine from years ago from years ago?
Imagine saying I on drugs when you take tramadol you're addicted to tramadol and you fucking drink your ass off
And you get stupid drunk that you take off your clothes on people's panels imagine that
Imagine not being able to have a normal conversation with a 51 year old. That's what I'm trying to figure out chairman
Imagine being so but her critical because cubes hate you. I love that but her critical
And so does Bruno with a zero imagine blaming me for shit when I wasn't even around
Oh, here you are still blabbing about me, right? What what exactly are you trying to accomplish here?
self-destruction
The real piece of shit you are and why not to be friends with beta, right?
I'm not gonna sit there and by the way, I was fucking asleep
I fell asleep on my stream when she was live about me imagine going on did I miss me?
Oh, who fucking who not really like I don't give a fuck, Bita
No, I don't know I just I I call her out one
I mean, I don't hate her, but she annoys me. I can't I mean, I hear you. I don't know if you're in me. I
Don't hate Bita, I don't really hate anybody on here besides maybe like same man
I might be the only person I truly genuinely hate like the like I would really put a bullet in his head if I could other than that
It's all just fuck around shit
Yeah you was being rude. You owe me an apology. Is that apology for me or for Kate? Let me know because you owe me an apology.
And I didn't call you a bitch. I didn't
Fucking go off on you. I just thought it was just give us just give us the apology man
Hey, don't go all into that. Just give us the apology. You owe me an apology. You okay to the apology
Okay, where's the apology yet just say you sorry to both of us
What you say, huh? I said, it's okay. I'm fine
Okay, well, she don't want her apology. I want mine though
So just give me my apology. Mr. Helpful yet. Here you are
Here you are
So much so that you had to go get on another alt to talk
Yeah, the link was there
The link was there I dropped a link when it was almost over. Yeah asked for a link. I would have
It's whatever
Hey, man, like you see what you did you hurt Kate feelings?
Come on, huh?
Now you don't upset Kate
They say I would I'm the only one that was afraid to you because I told you about the clip
Nobody else told you about the clip. I told you about the clip
You hadn't you hadn't seen her cook you so I was helping you out
So just just say just be thankful that let's say that I was in your corner and I was helping you out
They don't don't be angry at us
But be the be the the one that did the cook man now you're threatening me be careful who you play with
Okay, well be careful who you play with
Damn
So weird
That's what I'm saying like people be people
That's how I'm saying like don't don't give the main thing for a troll is to get get to get your attention and
Trigger you so don't even give them no attention. Just ignore
They say when I be a shiny shit that motherfucker Patrick got Bepa tell you that motherfucker
Patrick got being that motherfucker spurging out and chat. I don't even fucking look at this shit
He just keep going on and on and on and on like fuck that shit man
Like certain people don't don't like
You you you a certain troll you a troll slash content creator
Kate so let's say people that's below you shouldn't get your attention. Don't just give your attention to anybody
Now you can't get no content off of that motherfucker man fuck him don't even give him no attention
Just hide his ass and give him the fuck out of here. Show him the door
Vanilla dice dice salutes
But don't don't don't even give him no attention on the knowledge of nothing. Just give him the fuck out of there
Yeah, I just wanted to finish the clip that was all
Guess what Patrick all up in psyches chat no way
That dude is a weirdo man
He was in somebody else chat talking shit about Shannon and Shannon seen that shit and then he gonna lie about it
That's wild
Like crystal. I'm really hurt crystal that you was talking about me after I've been nothing but nice to you
You said she felt like you were taking beta side and I don't think she understood that just by saying beta cooked you
Wasn't necessarily taking her side. I don't fuck with beta. I don't like beta. All I'm saying was she was cooking
Like I don't fuck with beta
You agree with her. Yeah, I'm just I just respect the good cook
Like I'm not a hater on somebody's cooking like I don't fuck with Victoria, but big big sometimes Victoria man
She'd be cooking motherfuckers. I
Don't like that bitch. I don't like that weird bitch, but I say she'd be cooking
She she probably was I say Victoria probably can talk to you for cooks for female cooks
That's how I put I give Shannon one I give
What I say I give troller to I give Boston three
You four beat a five. Can you can you respect that? Can you respect that?
Yeah, I don't even think I'm not gonna cook no when you be raging you be cooking
But it I say it got it gotta be to raise Kate it can't be the normal Kate
We just observed the content crystal and we joy it sometimes. That's why we're here
Facts crystal I say you can't take everything to heart man like
Pack yourself up. He put the content out there cuz I say I don't watch beta
So he put the content out there. I enjoyed the content and then I say Kate was up here
She was live so a lot of people didn't see it cuz I guess they not subbed to pack yourself up
So I said we just bring a new eyes on it and out to me. I thought she cooked you and what what's the poll that?
Oh
Let's see
With 44 votes, I'll end it 80% of the people said yes see I'm not the only one crystal
Out of 44 people 80% of them said that be the cook you
Like I like to say I don't fuck with be the but saying be the be the be cooking man
And I don't really agree with Bita
Like beat it like beat it uncooked Kate be the be the half cooked K-dash
Yes, she has cooked you
Yeah, I'll cook you
She cooked the fucking I say she cooked a lot of people man
A lot a lot of females she have cooked and a lot of dudes let's say that her and that whole rage and shit
She was cooking that nigga then
I said be to be cooking man
Now y'all I'm saying I got to give her her props on that
That's he but Crystal no she never even seen it so let she she never even seen the cook so I helped her out
I just want to apology crystal. That's it
The site come back back in your stream
No, what is he saying now? What is he saying now? So is he apologizing? He's saying now
You go you're gonna go over there and join
No, probably not
Cuz Q's up there and I'm good you blame me for what?
Come on, man
What I do all I did was just bring the cat here in silicone
Want to know who all these dudes see fucking
You want to know why you ain't one yeah, that's what I'm saying like shit like she need to open them legs up for me
Like you see if she not why I mean so with a gassy date he black so I mean it can't be that
Like dang like like crystal crystal I'm a content curator
So you can't open them legs up to me and I'm just I'm just going off of what beta said
That's be to say you be fucking these content creators. So like I am Kate Kate. Will you consider me a content creator?
Sure, okay, see
That's a lot crystal my DMs is open
Me well now I blocked her I forgot I did block her man. You block crystal
Yeah, cuz I didn't like that shit with she fucking out it that me and her was talking behind the scenes. I didn't like that
And then we we had that private uh that private group and shit
Then she invited you and I think Bruno in there. I end up leaving that shit and blocking her ass
Yes, yes, Audrey, I'm alive
Hey Audrey
Refund Kate. Yeah refund Kate
Refund Kate for what?
I don't know
So that that that came money with the child support man. I say she helped she helped me out
Let's say she helped me get my child support down. So I appreciate that and
People are really gonna believe that too that that 20 that 25,000. She gave me help
25,000 yeah, I appreciate that
She's always doing weird group chats like that. Oh Lord
Cool, who they talking about crystal
Here
To lose to my girl chicken cakes
Seem Pico today
He ain't been running the minute have you
Not a last couple streams anyway. I
Hope I didn't scare Pico off. You shot you did you shout out chicken cakes?
Hi chicken cakes. Yeah, so sure some love
Damn
You say psyche didn't come back
Yeah, come back yet. I thought he'd be back by now
I'm surprised. He's not I want to see what Chris was hold on. Let's see
Barbs a piece. I mean not barbie there's a piece of shit
Anyone who has who has any sense and likes Vita y'all are just as bad as her, you know
Barb is a
I was watching
And I'm learning about corn snakes and
All right
You want to watch this
No, I mean I don't have to I'm not about to appear that long anyway
Yeah, I don't think she really I skipped the shit talking. Okay. Let me go back
But I'm saying was she apologizing
We need some
The thing is I don't give a fuck these people that find cookie person
I truly genuinely hate like the like I would really put a bullet in his head if I could other than that
I mean, I think it's about me. Oh fucking who like I don't give a fuck Vita
No, I don't think you know, I guess I I call her out when she annoys me
Yeah, I hear you. I mean, I don't hate her, but she annoys me. I can't I mean I hear you. I don't know if you hear me. I
Don't hate you though, I don't really hate anybody on here besides maybe like Sam, man
I might be the only person I truly genuinely hate like the like I would really put a bullet in his head if I could other than that
It's all just fuck around shit
Okay, sorry my thing was like fucked up. Can you hear me?
Q yeah
These people that find cooking entertaining. It's fucking dumb right bar. She's literally talking so much shit on me talking about my life
I didn't know it's a crime to be friend and ex when he gets sober, right?
Like I'm sorry beta. Who are you to judge anyone with your bush vagina of a bush? At least mine is fucking clean
No, I mean we could talk about a dark hole
Barbs of heat. I mean not barbita's a piece of shit anyone who has who has any sense and likes beta y'all are just as bad as her
I don't know
I was watching
I'm learning about corn snakes and
Let me go back a little more. I don't I don't yeah, hey beta. I don't really hate anybody on here
Because I don't care to listen to stupid shit about me. I don't
If people actually think I get to find what comes out of beta's mouth, I don't give a fuck
I don't know. I don't I'm not gonna look for it. It's not
Fuck Jimmy
They're fixed now. Good. It's just something to trigger her because she's easily
That's more believable than beta pulling the whiskers
Yeah
Yeah, all right. I'm good. I'm not
Yeah, he said something about how I can hate him for um
Saying the end word and being racist, but he'll never um
What he's never done to me what Barry's done to me
Uh, by exposing my nudes and what is new? What is new with what news that I exposed? I supposed to ask Pete
You already showed your ass anyway
I've never talked about your kids. That's them. That's the most important thing. I never talked about your kids
I never said shit about your kids
So actually he did worse what I mean what the shit I did or him talking about your kids, which one is worse to you?
I mean
Hello
Talking about my kids is pretty low
But I don't I don't even think the two things are like comparable there. I can't compare you two
Anyway, like there isn't comparing fucking
You who's nobody to me
Right like it's just I just don't think you can compare the two
I don't know why he even put himself on a level to be like oh well Barry did this to you, but I'm bad guy. Yeah, you're
I don't know. I just think it's weird dizzy. That's what I'm saying, but like he like he's
Sitting up here pointing the finger like he's so he's so obsessed with fucking a gay and shit and and what gay is dude
But this motherfucker spitting on women. He is sorting women
So like how the fuck is you talking about this motherfucker when you doing bad shit yourself?
And he I say he acting like he the
Like the poster boy you're calling him out on that shit when motherfuckers been calling him out on that shit
Like you not the first person to call him out on that shit
Like motherfuckers was calling him out on that shit two three years prior. Oh
Zaya on the groom. Yeah, he's not some pioneer of the anti Zaya
Yeah, that's what that's what he tried to make it seem like like he the pioneer and he the only one that stood
That stood up and standing up and this and that
Like my fuckers been talking about him about that shit. Like you're not the first one
Like the information you got you got from somebody from another community like that shit been out there
Who who she's talking about retarded
I think I think it's a majority of them chicks that come from the Carter verse man. I don't think they got it off
Like I had I had I had to excuse myself because like it was just like crazy man
Like I'm sitting up there trying to middle man trying to get her in and caring and shit the
So like at least be cordial and shit and like like they talking and shit
They getting along they saying ain't gonna do this they ain't gonna do that and then later on that day or the next day
They back beefing cuz this person did this that person did that and then like oh well tell her
I'm gonna take it down and she could take this down. I'm like fuck this shit, man. I'm not dealing with that shit. I
Don't know how I don't know how you
Nope
Nope. Nope. Nope. I'd block Karen
Well, I said it I didn't have no issue with Karen
But then when that whole that whole shit came out with the with the bread and Q and then
Old girl put that shit out of bar her saying and I gg er I said hell
No, I'm not fucking her down and then she just kept sending the same shit and I kept telling her
I don't care like I don't know who the fuck that Ella petty bitch is at all like I don't know who she is
So why the fuck are you keep telling me about what she's doing and what she's saying? Like I don't care. I do not watch her
Like she don't talk about shit that I'm probably interested in watching like so quit bringing her up
I say the whole barb and all them. I don't know who they is like
She trying to drag you into all their nonsense, yeah
Kicking cake is my backup channel. It's my backup channel, hun. Like I was gonna I was gonna do an interview with um,
But um, I think it was Nancy
But then I don't know like they said they'd be watching. I said, I don't know. I think a lot of them females
I think they'd be having alts. I think they'd be having alts in here
And like they be around cuz like like Nancy far as I knew I thought she was like away and shit
But then like she's seeing stuff that's going on and and I say she ended up not doing the interview or whatever
Well, if you think about it right now, there's 36 people watching but only like a few chatting
There's an awful lot of people that we don't know
Who it is, you know what I mean that are watching
Watching all these all these arts I say these these new all that be popping up. They'd be knowing everything
But just just been coming around
right
It's like there might be 10 chatting but then okay the other 27 people who was that it can be no name
You know what I mean? I was just find that interesting or like
Yeah, like when you look at the chat participants versus how many is watching and it's like, okay. Well, who are all those other people?
Are they people that never chat?
Are they are they?
Are they true? I don't know. I just think that's the or like even me with my subscribers
I look at and I have 1700 subscribers
But I only really know a
Handful, you know what I mean?
Who comment so who are all of the other?
Say fifteen hundred people
What they'd be watching
Subbed to me, you know what I mean? Yeah
Like it's the people that that lurk
That
That make me go home how many people are lurkers and what are they lurking for?
Don't know blogger lurks. Oh for sure cuz he always knows everything that's going on
Damn why he just don't type
Mmm
No, I think I think clumsy would type if he was if he was watching
I don't think clumsy would lurk
Yeah, he does admit it blogger old say that he
Thank you, you know, you know, he was still around. Oh, yeah, he's around looking like a 70s porn star
Living in his truck
Damn his mama kicked him out
Yeah, a couple months ago
Damn
Fuck you got into a caretaker or something. Damn
So this motherfucker living in his vehicle
Yeah, God damn that's fucked up
Damn, oh he beat the caretaker I
Mm-hmm. Damn
I just I knew they got into it. I didn't know it was physical
I'll say you you say he the car communities like the car communities like sleeping in his car
Sleeping in his truck is f-150. Yeah, but beef said that he's uh, he's the car community now, so
Yeah, well the truck community
So I mean is he's he's like living in like a RV park. Well, he just
Just living in parking spots
Damn, so he on that fucking what's that other dude that used to sleep in his car or still do
Fucking Nana
Damn, he's been around in a while. Have you
The father the droop, what's his name?
Can you hear me? Hello, can you hear me?
Hello damn I'm like Nana Nana Nana
Car culture
That's funny
I keep watching to see if psyche came back
No, and damn well the minute I end he's gonna go live
Lowkey's here at Newsy. Hey lowkey, how are you sunshine?
Anyone remember the cool Brandon had living there last year? Yeah, that methed out looking thing
You should cover some ranny and Chevrolet something to keep him offline. He needs to beg for food soon
What's going on
What's going on with oh here he goes you're back
Yeah, something's wrong my sound like I was talking and I seen your stuff moving, but I couldn't hear you
Nana is who you were thinking up. Yeah. Yeah, no, no
Yeah, that's fucked up damn
Now what and that's the thing like if he homeless why not get your life together instead of fucking still going live
Right like my fucking brother go live then go fucking put an application in and go get work
Damn but he should have knew that was coming he should have prepared it so
That's why you don't be fucking doing this shit you doing like why the fuck is you doing this shit you doing if I met somebody else
How's why would I be dealing with online bullshit?
Now I'll be trying like say trying to save up as much money as I can so I can get my own place. I
Guess he's been selling stuff. Maybe doing resale stuff trying to make money that way, but
Yeah, he gonna make that was money
Come on fucking making making a happy meal money
Sure ain't enough to fucking put a roof over his head. No, that's for sure
Like take care of real life people like this internet to be here when you get back take care of real life
If you fucking living in your car
Like you need to fucking actually fucking
Think about your life choices and not be on the fucking internet
And be on fucking in indeed and career builder
Using a chat GPT
The fucking help with your resume
That's one thing I'll give Tommy, you know he uh
He might have like his drugs, but
He he may not keep a job all the time he may not last long at a job, but he stays employed
You know what I mean? Like he loses a job. He will go get another one. I will give him that
He ain't afraid to work
facts
So I appreciate that about Tommy
Just want to sit and beg online
And it's a good thing that he got a car cuz what if he had no car then he'd be sleeping underneath a bridge
Yeah
Hey
That's fucked up man to know that you that close
To fucking be and live it to live it on the streets
He might get fired, but he always get another one or quit
He might get fired for smoking weed on the job. Oh my god that one time when he got fired
He was streaming on his break
Smoking he got caught he comes back live like ten minutes later, man. I got fired
Okay, glow. Hey, glow. You could talk glow Z and ain't here. Oh going out of chicken cakes
Yeah, but with glow glow can still speak I say is impulse not here
Cakes rather stick up for people driving by kids school and screaming and she's the mother
Damn
Yes, do your nails on the bedroom floor by the cat litter cakes damn
Cooking
Cakes did did defend them hard that is true Kate look she she made a mistake
She didn't know what she was saying at the time. She said that she was that she was drunk
I
Say cake cakes just they say eventually cakes will talk about the situation if she haven't already
Did she talk about it? Yeah?
She was on the fucking panel with them the next day
damn
Recapping her appearance
What does she say I don't know I didn't fucking um
I didn't watch it. Crystal was just showing that cakes was on panel with them as they were reviewing crystal and cakes being on panel, getting pressed.
Damn.
Hey, two white cups. Mwah. Psyche gave tricks. AIDS. That's why the camera...
Damn
And who was it who was that you were saying was that site you were saying that something about you donated thousands
Sikes said I donated thousands to Zaya
There was Zaya said that
Zaya is going around telling people I donated thousands
He got that shit from Elmo right
So why would you like to say
he supposedly trolled with the truth so I mean what like what part of that is the truth
that's what i'm trying to figure out do you realize that that would be
I didn't donate 666 fucking times.
No, but he said thousands.
So thousands, that's a plural.
So what, the 666 times is one hundred thousand?
It would have meant 666 donations at $3 a pop.
I mean, donate no 666 times.
Then what the fuck do it matter?
Don't let cakes fool you Barry. She stood on stood on it on Zayas last night
I didn't hear all that
damn hammer and
I stood on what I said last night and clarified any questions. You don't like me so it won't matter what I say or do
So I mean, so what does she stand on she stood on what fuck fuck Brandon Q, but she's still fucking with Gaia
Yeah, basically
That she don't have a problem with
She doesn't she doesn't condone the driving by the school, but she don't have a problem with there
Basically is what I
gathered
I mean, that's that's her that's her opinion. I mean she she has the right to have it
But I mean if that's the case and to me she's sitting down could deal cute in
I mean branding cute
Yeah, cause how can you have issues with one and not the other?
Oh, yeah, I'm on my backup channel because I was restreaming psyche
So just in case he got a wild hair to clap me. No hammer says he was screaming it, too
She was screaming it
Screaming what I'm saying, but I mean, can you can you really can you really put a level on the on a predator?
Can you put a level on a predator?
Predators a predator. Yeah, so I mean that's what I'm saying. She's saying that he worse
Well, he on another level
But I mean, can you really put a level on a predator?
It's either they are or they or they aren't
That's why pack your pack yourself up should have did a clip of that, but I just I just can't stand to listen to his voice and her voice.
I just can't stand
Sorry
Two white cubs. Yeah, no, I just went live because I was restreaming psyche. He didn't last long though
Everybody getting concrete and dildos
Yeah, that's what I'm saying like you can't you can't hate you can't fucking say you don't like
Brandy Q and what he do but then you support somebody else
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about for a ball
The shit Brandon doing is current day and keeps getting worse. He will be on the news one day mark my words
Okay, well
But he does he just didn't he just didn't he just pull up the fucking drove the fucking Florida the fucking pull-up on trolling
Yes, so it's all right for him to harass women
evidently
That's what I'm saying. So I mean, what's the difference between him and Brandy Q?
Now maybe I say people gonna like who they gonna like
I just don't fuck with them.
I don't fuck with them.
He claims he he claims he's not bothered by me. Mm-hmm. Whatever
I'm always on my a game. Get the fuck out of here Audrey. I'm not as high though. I probably need to go smoke some weed
Salute the hammer
No, he didn't get a porn bomb. No one chatted in his chat for like 10 minutes to wake up
And so he he quit because no one was chatting. We have he had like
13 people watching and we had like 30 watching over here and no one chatted for 10 minutes
This is great
I say you you could like who you want to like cakes, but let's say people that the masses it is
So I said when you come on panel or you and chat they are gonna press you
for fucking with with with him and fucking with them and like and having something to say about um
about Brandon Q
So I mean, so I say if you want to I say if you want to fight they battles
They're not gonna fight it for you
Salute to black rg
He needs to ebag for cigars and mcdonald soon
Some people live day-to-day. He lives hour by hour fax. That's a good way to put it. He's sure the fuck does
Hey, RG
So he is in Brandon Q's chat yikes go figure
He's the only one then
Oh, wow. Here's Psyche's chats and Brandy Brandon Q's. Yo, buddy.
LOL. I'm in your army now.
Nice music. Yep, I'm here.
I'm in your army now.
Yikes.
What? The booty game? The booty game army?
I guess.
Yeah, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche only fucking went for some dick.
Some dick or money
No, people actually donate to psyche. That's the sad part. There are people that donate to him
He will put on this poor fucking me
Pity party and somebody will send him fucking groceries. Somebody will send him door-dash with fucking Mike's hard lemonade
It's pathetic
There are people that literally feel bad for him
And still to this day are donating. No, I haven't donated to psyche in a minute
Maybe like a year a year or so
The fleas bit psyche and getting dust
He should left of him he's withering away that or they get drunk
He was drinking tequila the other night
I'm on his ass dude. I am on his ass. If I am available and he streams, I am
re-streaming him. That's all there is to it.
Dude lives in a $3,000 a month apartment but poor him.
Yep, that's what I don't get. Like the man lives in Redondo Beach.
Um, how is everything paid for but people still feel bad for him? It's it's insane to me
No, no, I pray but all right
Hold on I'll be right back
He does. No, he doesn't appreciate it at all. And I think that's what bothers me is like he's not grateful. He feels very entitled.
And it's sad.
It's fucking pathetic.
You can't take care of his damn self. No, he's fucking 40, 50, some years old and literally
Has to beg for tall boys
It's not an apartment it's a contamination facility his family stores them at
He's got to be the most unhealthy mother fucker he eats McDonald's every day how hasn't he gained weight, right?
McDonald's and coffee
It only pays for one coffee a day and then goes back to McDonald's all day long to get fruit refills. It's fucking weird
You really think he's got a tapeworm and that's why he's so skinny
Feel bad for his toilet
You know
Nasty what'd you say?
They said feel bad for psyches toilet
All he's just fucking McDonald's and coffee and fucking
Taco, what about the fifth taco? He don't do those no more. Don't even eat them anymore
He literally all he eats is fucking McDonald's
Told you man when he used that cheap tissue and when he wiped his ass and shit that it goes through the tissue
That's why his fingernails be so dirty
It's boo boo on his nails
Nasty
Nobody nobody. Hey you salute to nobody
AIDS
You he used that he used that one plot
He probably steal the toilet paper from McDonald's to
Like that cup
Hell yeah, the one cup that he keeps taking back
How would you think that cup is?
No, I do think he gets a new one like every day or two and he'll get the like he'll use his rewards for the coffee
Or he'll get like a dollar coffee because they're only like a dollar and then he goes back all day long
Damn you don't have no beer as a one-ply fetish
This poor family proud of him, I think they're probably embarrassed they're probably just grateful he leaves them the fuck alone
Yeah
That's what I'm saying. They probably just happy he on line and he's not fucking bothering them
He over there he over there eating them cats people. I'm telling you he over there eating them cats
Well, he first came over here. He had like nine cats now. He only got like what two three cats
He claiming that they ain't coming back, but I think he over there eating them because he don't he don't be eating like that
Like I don't know what that guy be doing with his money to where he be having a big and shit
That's unless his family got him like on the strict allowance
So we're like they only like give him like certain shit, but I say food should be like a necessity. I
Think he does have a very strict allowance
But I mean I think they watch everything that he spends
So I mean so I mean do they do you think they put like groceries in this fridge rather every month? I
Don't know I
Don't know but he don't seem like that a cook though
No, and Mike
Last week or the week before someone bought him a whole bunch of groceries and he literally was eating it all like that day
Just mowing everything down
Like a like he like a savage
All in the one day. He was eating shrimp. He was eating something else. He was eating something else
And then you know after McDonald's instead of eating the chicken sandwiches and the groceries that someone bought for him
That's what I don't get. Why doesn't he fuck? Why can't he work? He considers he considers YouTube a job for one
And I wish I wish that never would have been put into his fucking head that YouTube is a job
No, I told him he had that discussion before I told him that YouTube isn't a job. It's a hobby
I mean he now he not making enough to be able to live off on if he making enough to live off on at that point
It's a job right now. It's just a hobby
Man, he's sitting up there putting all that money in that fucking AI bullshit and they making no money off of it
Especially with him not being monetized
So he just paying all that money for that bullshit as AI shit and they making no money off of it
Yeah, they were saying like it all costs money all the
Like all the different things that he uses for the AI is all subscriptions. He has to pay for heartbeats and all this shit
But yet
Fucking is still still has to beg for money. Then um, I asked what happened to the daughters
They said he couldn't afford them anymore. He stopped paying the prescription or there's some scription
the whole daughters the AI daughters he had AI daughters and
Now you don't hear about them anymore
Yeah, yeah, daughters. Hmm cuz I don't watch them like I'm subbed to him
But I don't watch him like all that fucking AI video shit. I don't be watching that shit
They don't tell my going his his chat or I watch him as if it's some shit going on and even in I don't even stay long
He had to pay for their heartbeats. Yes, I don't understand it. I don't get it, but he literally had to pay
Yeah, that's some weird ass shit right there. I'm never even seen it
If he was rich as a child, then maybe he didn't learn the real struggle now
He is and he doesn't know how to handle it. He's going mental
Fucking I don't know what it is. I think he's very entitled and he thinks everything should just be handed to him
He's been entitled his whole life
and the reason his family doesn't give him much freedom
with the money is because he squanders it all on drugs.
And I think he probably,
they probably had to bail him out enough.
And so they give him just enough to get by.
And then he probably squanders that anyway.
And then he gets down to the end of the month
and he has nothing left and he has to beg for everything.
Like I don't think they would approve of him. I know at one point. He was saying he used his card certain places
And I feel like it's because they watch where he spends his money
They said he had a boyfriend too. Oh, yeah, that's right. He did. I think he did have an AI boyfriend at one point. Yeah
I think his family owns that building and just paid for the bills for the apartment, really?
Like, sense.
Give them enough to keep them out of their hair. Yep, and enough to get by.
a bunch of drugs. I can't
attack him for that because I'm
a lifelong inheritance leech
myself. Lucky you. Share some
of that with me there, Moshe.
Want to share some of your
inheritance money, Moshe?
I can cook good. Make meals
and shit.
I'll come be an inheritance leech with you. I
Make you some macaroni and tea
macaroni and tea. I
Do make good macaroni and cheese. It's not my favorite thing to make though
I make a mean roast
Yeah, so it looked like he's he's taking on a lot of Alex shit now she must be his uh
She must be meant to her
Oh, yeah. That's they're back on again. You know, she she shut them out for the longest time now of a sudden they're back on. She's condoning, you know, she changed your opinion on on.
Zaya, again.
What?
As far as what?
The 16 and 19 that it's okay.
That's how I don't even listen to her to lose the mermaid
On the mac and cheese. Sorry
Going live camming up in my house. Just it doesn't it doesn't work
In my kitchen, I just the whole setup it would be it would be too much
Hey mermaid, how are you sunshine?
Cake set up a lot. I want I saw that I thought I was crazy
Kicks, why didn't you go live you teasing the people?
You know buddy you think so maybe
Come on psyche go live again, that's what we're here for
He you know, he's watching
He's so watching
Sure, hey, it's like take the link. I know you watching psych take the link
We got questions the eggs
I'll drop the link
What's that out there, Gish?
Gishy here? Hello, doll!
Kitten cakes?
Hi, hi, hi.
So cute. Take it. Pause.
He's too busy in Brandon's.
Fuck.
I'm I'm in your army now. Get the fuck out of here. He said he told brandy in his army. Yeah
They bought to be fucking
And then just a little bit ago y'all I made the mistake of going to the x-rated room in
Discord because I saw it as I had something unread just while I was on stream and
It was a fucking picture of him fisting his asshole
Fucking discord for fucking gamble
cool
Brandon Q
Hell no, like that was a real video
Yes, he really did it
Go there RG, I'm gonna tag you just for that. I'm gonna tag you you said the fuck. Yep
RG
What do you do? What do you do?
How do you know it gets tagged?
He had the phone. He had the phone on the tripod.
I guess they had it zoomed in on his ass.
Yeah, he's on the bed and he's got his legs in the air.
That's a nasty shit man.
Playing with his butthole.
So he bought he bought a tripod.
So I'll say it so he bought a tripod just for that boy's fault. I don't know. I don't maybe maybe
He was cropped up on his desk. I
Don't know but oh there he is on all fours
What the fuck?
Yeah, oh wait, oh there he's
What in the hell why why am I doing this to myself? Oh
Y'all
Sorry RG I
Had to see it so somebody else had to I've seen my fear share of anus is reason enough to leave this court
Jesus
Anybody else want to see it? I'll tag you
Fucking Christ, I just
Did you tag low-key? I'm pretty sure low-key want to see it. Is she a freaks a lot Anita Blunt?
Low-key a fucking freak low-key you here
Yes, you do deserve it for the Janet stuff
And then he's like at the end
He, he's laying in bed and he's like holding his phone up to his face and he looks like he just got done like busting a nut like he was so pleased with himself. He's all sweaty.
I take Loki just for fun anguish.
Yeah, Loki want to see that shit.
Hey, hold on. I made it. I took all four baby mamas out tonight together and nobody fought over my cock
Good get where's it? He didn't take me out. I'm gonna be baby mama number five. You just don't know it
Yeah, right
Fucking my eggs are scrambled. No more kids coming out of this cuter
Cakes I think Kate I think chicken cakes is Christine close your eyes and listen to them speak and you won't be able to distinguish
They are strikingly similar
I'm all my way Barry Barry's trying to give me away
Ain't no trying you already gone
You Pico you Pico you Pico you belong to Pico and juice all right what you want me to do
Meanwhile neither of them claim me
Maybe they are. You're welcome, Gesh.
How do you feel about what you just saw? Do you have any extra commentary?
Hot. Don't bring that name up.
Shut up, Bixper.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I can direct you where to go. Who the hell is hamster? Oh God.
Oh, you're a hamster.
Hamster had a thumb-sized dick and said I appreciate it. I deserved it.
No, sir. No, I don't.
He was trying to stick all that one-inch cock in a cake.
He was trying to put the whole one-inch in there.
Balls deep. Yeah, he said you gonna get this shit
Like that mom that motherfucker actually had like a fucking pinky-sized dick
But he actually he actually was proud to show that shit off
You deserve this like what it's all yours, Kate
That's what I deserve. Damn. Why does life hate me so much?
That's good living. It ain't the size of the boat.
Facts holding. It was, it was that small.
It ain't the size of the boat.
He said he knew what he was doing with that.
It was in his underwear. Thank God. Thank you. It was it was in it was in his boxers. I didn't I didn't see it like
Like out there
It was in his boxers and he had it on hard
That motherfucker was small as hell I
Could probably show it good night. Yeah, you still got it. I have it
probably not
You got it. You got it. You'd be playing with your shit with that picture
I'm pretty sure
No, I think it was in the other discord
But I went it went it. Well, I don't know because you had a new account
Huh, oh it was your dick
I came across
Yeah
Salute the holder
Hold on, I'll show you all if I can find it because that shit's funny as hell nobody
He was he was proud he was proud to show that shit off you deserve this
You know who would have it? I know who has it
fishy
No
fucking
Quarter cow. He's still around
So
You got a new account
Yeah, what's I can't remember what he's under now damn in discord anyway, but um
He's in chats too under a new art
No
He must come over here. He must don't fuck with you. No, he does he comes on he comes in the other one. Oh
I haven't seen
Pepe unless you got a new art Pepe. Yeah, I haven't seen them
Damn it. I don't think I have it. I don't think I saved it. Damn. Why you ain't say that shit?
No, they said juice got it. Yeah, juice probably got it. I'm pretty sure he got it
Anything pretending the dicks he got it
There it is
Yeah, we found it people we found it juice sent it to her we found it
Shout out the juice wait until y'all see this
Shut up the juice for keeping that dick pic for us and then so mind you. I'm trolling the guy
So I have to keep up with
appearances
And I tell him thank you very nice. Hold on
You wanted that dig
Damn, that's that shit on hard too
Hey ladies, hey ladies, tell me what y'all think with that y'all like that
Come on ladies y'all fucking with that
Y'all fucking with that ladies? Come on, let me know.
And to tell me that's all I deserve
I've said but he he and he and uh he in australia. So maybe in australia. Maybe that's let's consider big
Oh my god
I'm guessing that's us
He said you deserve all that
Just imagine just imagine putting that shit in your mouth
He said you deserve all of that
I
For me damn
Yeah, me and me and Hester about the same size
I can I can send you a picture just like say, uh,
Audrey just let me know I can send you a picture and shit you can rate it
Oh my god
It's completely unacceptable.
You could be my newest angel.
BBT, be quick.
Lisa, you deserve all this, baby.
I said thanks, very nice.
And then I immediately screen shot it sent it to everybody
That's fucked up how you did that guy she she she made that dude leave the discord after that
Like the dude was so embarrassed he left the discord after he revenge porn me though
Oh my god, that shit was so fucking funny.
I mean, you put his dick pic out there.
Ice Poseidon's nose is bigger than that.
Oh, shut up.
Audrey says send it to Cakesberry.
So what?
Your dick pic.
Cake cakes you asking for it. You want you want the dick pic? I sent it to you cakes. Just let me know
Santa's is just a penis
She wants it she didn't say that
She said absolutely not get the hell out of here she wants that BBC you just say absolutely not
Senator an IG
This this level just like say let me know cakes. I say don't they don't have to people don't people in chat
Don't have to know if you that big of a freak like that
No means yes to cakes
damn
She said please send me that shit
Until a lot of people want the BBC's they they want the pictures of the BBC's
Oh, my God. I can't believe I found that.
So you see she said no.
She says she don't need to see that.
Oh, come on, Cakes.
I was in I was in I was in troller chat this morning
Say see it's good to see that she's she's given her life to the Lord
That's what I like to see man. Like she's a she's a change individual
So what like the old troller I can't judge her off of what she did in her past because
Now she's gave she's given her life to the Lord. So now like she's she's a changed person
I'm a changed person. So I say me and her is both moving in the in the right direction of being changed people
Oh, whatever
I like I like to go over there and listen to her
Like I say spread the word and I like I like how she's how she's doing it like the way she's dressed
When she's given the word of God
She's a real she's a real love like I say a real Christian. I like to see that
Yeah, I'm willing to give the the the Christian troller a
Second chance a third chance for chance. I'm not many chances. I give her
But I'm willing to try this one out because I like I like the the word that she's like have you have you ever watched her
Live like she gives like a scripture that she reads
Like throughout her life. I really appreciate that
I'm telling you like if it's some people if it's some people out there that's that's golly people like go check her out man
I it's a Christian channel
See
Huh, you just like to look at the tits is I'm going to listen to the word the word
I'm saying she got me believing now
Man she's a changed person I say I'm changing
Did you see that she's claiming that she is too skinny so she wants to gain weight to me
That means it's not working for her and she'd rather eat. Yeah
Yeah, pretty much
Happy Mother's Day
Stop it with that paragraph
Trippy getting called out for his paragraphs. Yo psych. Yo psycho twin here
Hey KK
Yeah, we're on the backup cuz I was restreaming psyche
That's it. She don't have them. She don't have them. Where me hose no more
That's it was like like years ago, man. She doesn't get that she cleared up
He said she got that shit cleared up
I'm telling you like go go over there man like say she reading is not the same trolling no more
It's a different trolling people the old troll is not around no more
This is a christian trolling and I said you just want to go over there and just like say listen to the word of god
That's the place to go
With tits
The word of God with it. Yeah, I'm saying that's that's how I like that's how I like to listen to the word of God
I like to listen and I like to have something to look at
She just need to adjust that camera down a little bit more and maybe maybe maybe you put some oil on her chest
Hell no
Some holy oil. Yeah
I'm saying that's why she's doing it. That's why she's doing it
She's doing it to bring people in because a lot of people they're not gonna listen to the word of God unless they got something
To look at so she brings them in by showing her breast off and then she hits them with the word of God
So make sure y'all go check her out man, I'm telling you
And
Come on
She says she don't want it Audrey unless Audrey is a cakes accountant and she pretended oh here go Alvaro
Hey, Alvaro
Hit uncle out with the word of God
You tore his G.O.D. crazy P.U.R.
See, K.K. saying that she's great.
See, let's give her another chance, people.
K, I can get you back over here. Just say the word.
I'm good. I'm good.
You sure?
Hoot Hoot. I'm an owl. I'm good.
Oh, you an owl now?
Hoot Hoot.
Damn.
Yeah, KK a flip flopper fucking that's the psycho twin
That's why that's why I understand like she she don't forgive Kate, but why she won't forgive cakes
I heard cakes was a good was a good team together
There was like a Woody Harrelson and fucking Wesley Snipes and shit for money train
You never seen money trying no get the fuck out of here and you say you you be
Fucking with a what with the niggas? I don't fuck you you fuck with the niggas, but you've never heard of money
Well with Jennifer Lopez
No, you need to check that out
What you what you mean that's the cakes man y'all y'all need to make up man
We need that we need that duo back together
KK was willing KK was willing to give you another chance
Damn gets never seen Friday get the fuck out of here
How the fuck gets never seen Friday? That's a classic
Man fuck dragon be beat man that fucking bitch keep crying and shit
That bitch care man. She missed she missed troll the friendship and troller not giving it back to her
If trolling if trolling would allow fucking dragon to come back she'll be fucking on her knees fucking
Taking the the the heaven gods for letting her fucking come back over there
But now she pissed off or she wanted she wanted to write long ass poems and shit
Yeah, I'll be I'll be coming in every time dragon post some shit and I see it
I'll be coming on there laughing laughing my ass off of her fucking dumb ass
She was over there kissing ass and trolling was just dragging her ass
That's what I'm saying. Trolla be cooking people man
Uh
Can we be done with the troll glace? I'm just saying she'd be cooking people man
Like you don't remember when she'd be cooking when she was cooking a green green machine
Not really
It was a while ago not really no y'all remember 11 color
Yeah, living color mad TV. I
Just was never in the Saturday night lie
People said he'd been waiting on this for years
But for the dragon versus
Troller mm-hmm
But I thought they I thought they was they they beef. I thought they beef all the time though
Not like this
I remember dragon was going at somebody in her chat. I think it might have been green teeth machine
I think them two didn't get along her and green machine didn't get along and
She took she took the green teeth
Side over dragon and she fucking went off on dragon for going out of green machine
Yeah, I'm dragon never like
Went went back at Troll of not like this
Dragon's even been in Skelly's chat.
Dragon versus Mermaid fights were always iconic.
Mermaid tracks a savage war.
Oh come on Mermaid.
I thought you two were like sisters.
You're not like sisters mermaid
Yeah, I thought they were sisters they're not friends guess that mermaid come on
Mermaid is good people out there
No, yeah, yeah JLo used to be the dancer on there
Yeah, they've been beefing
Yeah, I don't fuck with dragon do dragon still come over here
Sometimes she probably don't know about this channel
Part of why you didn't know why you didn't tag it on your main channel
I, I shared it on my community post.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you don't know if the case went out either.
I mean, I wasn't, I didn't intend for it to turn into a live, but oh well.
You know, I thought I was just going to restream him and hop off.
But here we are, two hours later.
Two and a half hours later.
No, he ain't he ain't coming back as he watching you. Mm-hmm. It's crystal still alive come on psyche take a lot of link. Oh
Let me see. Yep
She got Q and Barb and Viva la Terry Davis on there where the fuck did Terry Davis come from does anybody know?
He's going to go live when I end and you know what I'm gonna do beep beep. I'm firing right back up
Damn, you know his ass like that. I'm on his ass like that
He's gonna he's gonna have to wait till I go to bed. Even then I still may wake up and restrain
Damn
Yeah, I ain't got no dedication right there
No, I doubt I'll wake up and restream, but if I'm awake and he's streaming
This weekend. No, I'm I'm restreaming
If I got the computer like I said before I was getting ready to just go fucking clean my kitchen
I was just gonna mute and let it play. I mean it don't
Shit once I got it playing don't take nothing. I didn't need to fucking sit there
I figured I'd check in on chat every now and then and just let it play, but it didn't work out like that because he
He rage quit
Over no one chatting
Psyche you can take a link
Talk to us
Yeah, and I like you got a lot of cats over there to watch the autumn cats you don't eat
Come on Psyche
Cates on Psyche like please on his cats. Amen.
Yeah, he's gonna go live and play victim. Oh, Cates picking on me.
Hmm.
The only reason I didn't restream him earlier is because Alex was on
and I didn't find that interesting at all. And so I was like, yeah, I'll let him have his piece.
I was watching other shit.
Crystal was on so I was like screw it, but
One time I watched a movie about vampires in the hood, but I can't remember the name of it vampires in the hood is wild
I thought it was vampires in Brooklyn
She's maybe is that it vampires in Brooklyn better one with Eddie Murphy and um, and Angela Bassett. Who said that?
Who asked you watch the
Yeah, I heard a vampire in Brooklyn with Eddie Murphy and Khadim Hardison and I say Angela Bassett
Vampires in the hood. I never heard that that must be some to be shit
Oh
She said she watched them about the empires in the hood, but she couldn't remember the name. So she said maybe that's it
I'm finishing right now. Um, yesterday while I was at work, I started watching, um,
The get the fuck out of here you watch a lot of porn
Not at work. Yes, you do. I haven't watched porn in a while
Watched trust me the false prophet. I'm almost done with that
That man on that man on fire is good on Netflix
The man on fire
Yeah, I think it's supposed to be like the one the movie with Denzel with Dakota Fanny
But they turn into a series
There's a series on Netflix that's pretty good
What are you watching right now?
Which one the one I was talking about
It's pretty good. I got a finished watching it. It's really interesting. It's about the FLDS
fucking extreme like fundamentalist Mormons and I
Don't know if you remember, um
When that trailer got pulled over and there were a bunch of people in the back of it
It's like these Mormon people. I don't know it's good. Oh
Lord of the Flies I have to watch it. I remember reading that book in school
The testament's I'm watching the testament. That's pretty good. That's like a spin-off to
the hand that was the hand hand maids tail
Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's like a spin-off on that but that's I know it's on Hulu, but I've been watching that that's pretty good
Yeah, I got I got that's why I got to get off is I got to watch my
What is it called a mayor country a share share of country?
You haven't
That's a good thing I'm thinking about watching the fireman one. Oh
My mom says that one's better
Yeah, I'm thinking about starting to watch that one because I'm caught up on the share of country and I'm caught up on
What's that other shit I watched?
That's been off to the fucking Yellowstone with the Sun
Marshall I'm caught up on that
So I say I might I might start watching that fire the fire country
Yeah, my mom says that she likes that one better than
the other one
Yeah, I'm about to I'm about to go but
Say salute to everybody like I say make sure y'all stay safe this weekend
Happy Mother's Day to all the mothers out there. Make sure y'all enjoy your day
For the people that got mothers make sure you check in on your mothers
And don't be like that bitch ass motherfucker Jimmy where you can't do shit for your mom and shit and fucking take her out
And fucking give her at least a card and some flowers and some shit like that
So let's say salute to all the mothers are the good mothers
Like I say even the bad ones because I mean I say it takes a lot to be able to bring a kid in this world
So I say just salute to all the mothers
Thank you
Yeah, salute to you Kate because you are a mother or so I
appreciate that
Yeah, happy Mother's Day to all the mothers
You know happy Mother's Day mamas
It's foil your mamas or your baby mamas or your wife's tomorrow
I'm gonna hop off here. I may be back if psyche
And well at one more thing for all the stud women there's mothers. This is your day
Don't take father's day father's day is not for you. You fucking stud bitches mother's day is for you
Don't try to take father's day. You are not me and father's day is for us like let us have our day
Don't try to take that shit away from us. Y'all need to be celebrating Mother's Day. All the fucking stud women
Mother's Day is for you. Not Father's Day. Get your own fucking shit. Get us get a stud day
Don't take Father's Day from us. Fuck y'all
No, that was a thing
Everybody have a good night. Like I said if if psyche goes live again
Maybe I'll go live and restream it. We'll see
Depends if I take my ass to bed and
Or not if I fall asleep, then I'm out, but
If he ends up going live in the next hour, I might be back. We'll see
Thanks for everybody for coming chicken cake Shane Adams. Gish kitten cakes myrrh made
Beep beep low battery
Well Damien
Black RG, Lady Bathory, Deebsie, Gish.
All the people that were in here tonight.
Thank you for coming.
We'll see you around.
Bye.